because i was forced to know who they are you're forced to know who they are so blue face is the
rapper who had that song uh tatiana and christian rock is the young lady who was on his little like
flavor of love type show on zeus network and then she ended up becoming like obsessed with him they
ended up being in a relationship she lost a tooth in the process then she got the tooth back and
they have been gallivanting all across these internets in a series of toxicity for the last
like two years and every time i see them it's like what is going on and now apparently she has
announced that she is pregnant so this is a letdown because let me tell y'all i don't know if this
relationship is like actually toxic or if they're just doing it for the gram either way it is toxic
for all of us who have to witness it and if a baby is brought into the mix then that's only gonna make
it worse good lord nails do you think this is real i'm just like you i don't know if it's real or not
i don't know because the stuff that we see everything i mean it's every day we see something
different with i'd be wondering if they're like sitting at the end of the day like what can we do
tomorrow like maybe they're actually like a very like easygoing couple and they're like sitting on
the couch watching netflix like cuddling each other like wondering what madness are we going to bring to
the world tomorrow
tomorrow